Life admin arrives as screenshots, receipts, voice notes, PDFs, and tangled thoughts.
LifeInbox gives everything one calm, private place to land.
Every account begins truly empty. There is no demo workspace:
each Appwrite record and file belongs only to the signed-in user.
One capture surface accepts text, images, PDFs, and voice.
I can organize actions or deliberately keep information as a permanent note.
This single thought contains three intentions: renew insurance, email Maya, and book a dentist.
I drop it in without organizing anything first.
GPT-5.6 Terra uses high reasoning and strict Structured Outputs
to separate every intent into three small, independent, source-grounded items.
Each draft exposes its evidence, confidence, date, priority, and missing information.
I can edit or remove anything before a single item is saved.
After approval, all three items persist in Appwrite, survive a refresh,
and flow into Today and the Inbox without losing their source context.
Smart Focus reduces the day to three clear moves and a quiet focus session.
Completed work stays searchable instead of disappearing.
Not everything is a task. Notes preserve complete reference information until I delete it,
without polluting Today with fake outstanding work.
When information becomes actionable, I turn the note into a linked task.
Life Threads keep the action, people, dates, and original context together.
Ask LifeInbox reasons only over my permissioned workspace.
It recommends the next move, explains why, and returns citations instead of unsupported advice.
Every citation opens its exact source item. LifeInbox Spotlight also finds
any task, note, person, or Thread without navigating through menus.
My data remains portable. LifeInbox exports a designed multipage PDF
with metrics, grouped items, notes, status, confidence, and page numbers.
The same clean workspace adapts to desktop, tablet, and phone, installs as a PWA,
keeps AI keys server-side, and supports complete deletion.
Codex helped turn my product direction into tested architecture, resilient AI, and a deployed experience.
LifeInbox: drop it in, understand it, move on.